

### **Contacts**

**L** +38 066 252 44 81

□ nonamezzz322@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/anatolii-vovchok-080481203/

@t\_vovchok

Nonamezzz322

### **Skills**

HTML5	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	0	0	0
CSS3	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	0	0	0
JavaScript	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	0	0	0
React.js	•	•	•	•	•	•	0	0	0	0
React-Redux	•	•	•	•	•	•	0	0	0	0
TypeScript	•	•	•	•	•	0	0	0	0	0
Opencart CMS	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	0	0	0
Firebase	•	•	•	•	•	0	0	0	0	0
MongoDB	•	•	•	•	•	0	0	0	0	0
GIT	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	0	0	0
Jest	•	•	•	•	•	0	0	0	0	0

# **Vovchok Anatoliy**

I have been studying Web development for 1.5+ years now. Has internship and startup experience, as well as freelance projects and part-time jobs. I am looking for a job where I can develop as a professional and work with modern JS frameworks and libraries. Always open to learning new things and, if necessary, ready to learn to use unfamiliar tools or programming languages. In my spare time, I am developing my own application in React + Express + MongoDb. In it, I try to use the latest technologies and keep the code clean with ESLint (airbnb).

### **Education**

2013-2016 Poltava University of Economics and Trade Bachelor degree. Specialist of finance.

2010-2013 Poltava Cooperative College. Junior srecialist degree. Specialist of finance.

# **Programming courses**

2018 Front-end developer, courses provided by "A-level" (Poltava).

# **Experience**

#### **Freelance**

Web developer | June 2020 - today

Working with online stores on Opencart. Editing existing ones and creating new ones. I also had experience in creating bots for Discord. Create multi-page landing for for cargo car service

#### Santehnika-online.ru

Content department specialist | June 2015 - today

Filling the online store with goods, updating the assortment, monitoring the relevance of information about goods on the site. Communication with wholesale suppliers. Resolving controversial issues related to the content on the site.

#### Peculiar Ventures, Poltava

Front-End Intern | December 2018 - May 2019

Internship and subsequent participation in the development of a startup web application in React, Redux, TypeScript, Webpack.

# Languages

English (pre-intermediate)

Ukrainian (native)

Russian (native)